<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shoaibashk</title><link>https://shoaibashk.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Shoaibashk</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 23:50:54 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shoaibashk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Own Flutter Interview Questions</title><link>https://shoaibashk.github.io/posts/my-own-flutter-interview-questions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 23:50:54 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://shoaibashk.github.io/posts/my-own-flutter-interview-questions/</guid><description>Here is my own collection of handpicked flutter interview questions for experienced flutter engineers.
What is Flutter? Link to heading Flutter is an open-source mobile application development framework created by Google. It allows developers to build native-looking mobile applications for both Android and iOS platforms using a single codebase. Flutter uses the Dart programming language, which is also developed by Google, and offers a wide range of customizable widgets that can be used to create stunning user interfaces.</description></item><item><title>Prepare for Flutter Interview</title><link>https://shoaibashk.github.io/posts/prepare-for-flutter-interview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 23:49:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://shoaibashk.github.io/posts/prepare-for-flutter-interview/</guid><description>How to prepare for flutter interview? Link to heading Preparing for a Flutter interview involves several steps, including reviewing the basics of the Flutter framework, familiarizing yourself with common interview questions, and practicing your coding skills. Here are some tips to help you prepare for a Flutter interview:
Review the Flutter documentation: Familiarize yourself with the basics of the Flutter framework, including widgets, state management, and asynchronous programming. Read through the official Flutter documentation, and practice building small apps to solidify your understanding.</description></item><item><title>Flutter Common Interview Questions</title><link>https://shoaibashk.github.io/posts/flutter-common-interview-questions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 23:44:06 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://shoaibashk.github.io/posts/flutter-common-interview-questions/</guid><description>Here are some common Flutter interview questions that you may encounter in a Flutter job interview:
What is Flutter, and how does it work? Flutter is an open-source mobile application development framework developed by Google. It uses the Dart programming language and allows developers to build natively compiled applications for mobile, web, and desktop from a single codebase.
What is the difference between Stateless and Stateful widgets in Flutter? Stateless widgets are widgets that do not change their state during the lifetime of the widget.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://shoaibashk.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:05:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://shoaibashk.github.io/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Dokcli An OpenAPI Documentation Tool</title><link>https://shoaibashk.github.io/projects/dokcli/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 09:59:11 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://shoaibashk.github.io/projects/dokcli/</guid><description>Dokcli is an OpenAPI Documentation tool, consisting of ⚡ - Link to heading built-in Rapidoc web component support Swagger &amp;amp; OpenAPI Spec Convenient way of hosting Api Documentation in 1 file For documentation and examples, please visit https://github.com/Shoaibashk/dokcli
🚧 Please keep in mind that Dokcli is still under active development ⚗️ and therefore full backward compatibility is not guaranteed before reaching v1.0.0
Overview ✨ Link to heading Dokcli could be downloaded directly as a standalone app for API Documentation using Swagger &amp;amp; OpenAPI spec file.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://shoaibashk.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 19:12:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://shoaibashk.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hello there ❗ Link to heading I&amp;rsquo;m Shoaib, a software developer from India 🇮🇳.
I do mostly web and mobile development.
I like to work on (C#, Go, JavaScript/TypeScript, React, Flutter)
Visit the Github website!</description></item></channel></rss>